Bob Bullock Campaigns papers, Inclusive: 1970-1996, Bulk: 1973-1996
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 1990 Campaign, 1973-1991; 5
  - Publications, 1987-1990; 19
    - News clippings, 1987-1990; 4
      - General, 1990 August (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - General, 1990 September (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - General, circa 1990 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Bullock Clips, Special, 1987 September (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Bullock Clips, Special, 1988 June (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Bullock Clips, Special, 1989 September (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Bullock Clips, Special, 1989 December (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Newsletters, 1987-1990; 5
      - Newsletters, 1987 September (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Newsletters, 1987 October (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Newsletters, 1988 January (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Newsletters, 1989 March (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Newsletters, 1989 April (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Newsletters, 1989 May (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Newsletters, 1989 June (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Newsletters, 1989 July (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Newsletters, 1989 August (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Newsletters, 1989 September (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Newsletters, 1989 Fall (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Newsletters, 1990 Spring (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Newsletters, circa 1990 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - Houston Apartment Association, Abode, 1990 October (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Texas State Teachers Association, Advocate, 1990 August-September (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Press Releases, 1987-1991; 6
      - Press Releases, 1987 September (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Press Releases, 1988 July (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - Press Releases, 1988 August (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - Press Releases, 1988 October (Box 36, Folder 39)
      - Press Releases, 1989 January (Box 36, Folder 40)
      - Press Releases, 1989 February (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - Press Releases, 1989 May (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - Press Releases, 1989 June (Box 36, Folder 43)
      - Press Releases, 1989 July (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - Press Releases, 1989 September (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - Press Releases, 1989 October (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - Press Releases, 1989 November 1-14 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Press Releases, 1989 November 16-30 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Press Releases, 1989 December (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases, 1990 January (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases, 1990 February (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, 1990 March (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Press Releases, 1990 April 10-13 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, 1990 April 17-25 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Press Releases, 1990 May (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Press Releases, 1990 June 4-15 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Press Releases, 1990 June 20-29 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Press Releases, 1990 July (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Press Releases, 1990 August 1-2 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Press Releases, 1990 August 3-13 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Press Releases, 1990 August 15-16 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Press Releases, 1990 August 22-27 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Press Releases, circa 1990 August (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Press Releases (1 of 2), 1990 September (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Press Releases (2 of 2), 1990 September (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Press Releases, 1990 October 2-12 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Press Releases (1 of 2), 1990 October 15-26 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Press Releases (2 of 2), 1990 October 15-26 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Press Releases, 1990 November (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases, 1990 December (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Press Releases, circa 1990 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Press Releases, 1991 January (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Press Releases, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1989-1990; 20
    - Correspondence System Report, 1989 May 11 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Weekly, 1990 January 1-7 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Weekly, 1990 January 8-12 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Weekly, 1990 January 15-19 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Weekly, 1990 January 29-February 4 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Weekly, 1990 February 5-18 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Weekly, 1990 February 19-March 4 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Weekly, 1990 March 5-18 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Weekly, 1990 March 19-31 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Weekly, 1990 April 1-15 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Weekly, 1990 April 16-29 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Weekly, 1990 April 30-May 13 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Weekly, 1990 May 14-27 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Weekly, 1990 May 28-June 8 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Weekly, 1990 June 11-22 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Weekly, 1990 June 25-July 6 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Weekly, 1990 July 8-21 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Weekly, 1990 July 23-August 3 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Weekly, 1990 August 6-17 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Weekly, 1990 August 20-24 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Weekly, 1990 August 27-September 1 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Weekly, 1990 September 3-7 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Weekly, 1990 September 10-14 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Weekly, 1990 September 17-21 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Weekly, 1990 September 24-28 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Weekly, 1990 October 1-5 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Weekly, 1990 October 8-12 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Weekly, 1990 October 15-19 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Weekly, 1990 October 22-27 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Weekly, 1990 October 28-November 9 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Weekly, 1990 November 12-16 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Weekly, 1990 November 19-23 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Weekly, 1990 November 26-December 9 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Weekly, 1990 December 10-14 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- 1994 Campaign, 1991-1995; 6
  The 1994 Campaign series is the second largest and has fourteen subseries, with several containing sub-subseries. This series also covers a campaign for Lieutenant Governor. The subseries include: General, Media/Advertising, Correspondence, Endorsements, Financial, Invitations - Fundraisers, Issues, Itineraries, Mosbacher, Notebooks, Polls, Position Papers, Publications, and Reports.
  General in 1994 Campaigns contains materials used in political campaigns, such flyers and bumper stickers. The Media/Advertising subseries holds campaign advertising materials like ads, information packets, correspondence, mailings, and radio ads. Correspondence has three sub-subseries and the Endorsements subseries has two sub-subseries. Financial in this series contains financial correspondence. Invitations reflect fundraising and campaign events for Bullock and other politicians. They include actual invitations and pledge cards. The Issues subseries has three sub-subseries. Itineraries includes folders of weekly and monthly calendars, and some related to Jan Bullock’s involvement. The Mosbacher subseries details Bullock’s Republican opposition Rob Mosbacher through contribution and expense reports, general campaign information, and news clippings. Notebooks holds a Senate Race analysis, while Polls contains information on election surveys, public attitude surveys, telephone surveys, polling reports, and analyses of polling information. Position papers detail Bullock’s position on critical issues such as crime and drugs. Publications contains four sub-subseries, and Reports contains Texas business reports.
  - General, 1993-1994; 1
    - Filing, 1993 December 3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Bumper Stickers: Bullock-Lt. Governor/’94, circa 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Flyer: Lieutenant Governor’s Race-Edwards Campaign Whipping Itself, circa 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Media/Advertising, 1991-1995; 2
    - Ad, “43 States Have an Income Tax, But Not Texas”, circa 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Ad, “The Challenge”, circa 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - News and Information Packet, circa 1994 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Public Relations: Gold Communications, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations: McKinnon Media, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Public Relations: Public Strategies, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1991 March (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1991 April (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1991 September (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Justice Mailing, circa 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Lobby Mailing, 1994 May (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Photo Slicks, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Political Ad, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Political Ad, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Radio, “Better Than The Best”, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Radio, “Independent”, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Radio, “Bust ‘Em”, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1993; 3
    The Correspondence subseries has three sub-subseries, organized by: Alpha, Form Letters, and Senators. It contains correspondence from individuals, other politicians, and campaign staff members.
    - Alpha, 1991-1992; 1
      - Agraz, Lidia, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 21)
      - Davenport, Michael W., 1991 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      - Flournoy, Mary M., 1992 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Kelly, Robert I., 1992 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Nash, Charles D. Jr., 1992 (Box 40, Folder 25)
      - Pemberton, Monette, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 26)
      - Sparks, Fred C., 1992 (Box 40, Folder 27)
      - Yontz, Caryl, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Form Letters, 1991-1993; 2
      - All Democratic Senators, 1991 April 12 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - All Democratic Senators, 1991 November 12 (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - All Democratic Senators, 1992 January 23 (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - All Democratic Senators, 1992 August 12 (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - All Democratic Senators, 1992 September 9 (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - All Democratic Senators, 1992 September 16 (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - All Lobby, 1991 March 25 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - All Lobby, 1991 April 5 (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - BB Contributors, 1991 April 18 (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - Basic Planning Mailout to Senators, 1992 April 15 (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - Bexar County Senators, 1993 June 23 (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - Bob Glasgow’s Campaign Letter, 1992 May 27 (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - Bob Parker List, 1993 April 26 (Box 40, Folder 41)
      - By Texas Consumer Association, 1993 March 24 (Box 40, Folder 42)
      - Campaign Volunteer Thank You Letter, 1993 September 22 (Box 40, Folder 43)
      - Coalition & Caucus Letters, 1992 June 9 (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Contributions Returned After Deadline, 1993 June 7 (Box 40, Folder 45)
      - Dallas Calling List, 1993 May 10 (Box 40, Folder 46)
      - Daily Editors-Texas, 1993 March 11 (Box 40, Folder 47)
      - Daily Newspaper Editors, 1991 May 14 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Democratic House Member, Franchise Tax, 1992 September 17 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Democrat Nominee, 1992 March 11 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Democrat Nominee, 1992 March 12 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Democratic Nominee For District Attorney Letter, 1990 March 23 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Democratic Party; Texas Democratic Party Chairs; Texas Democratic Executive Committee and Officers, 1991 April 16 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Democrat Re-Election Letter, 1992 March 11 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Democrat Re-Election Letter, 1992 March 12 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Democrat & Republican Election Letter, 1992 March 12 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Democratic National Committee, 1992 June 10 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Democratic Nominee, Election Night, 1992 April 15 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Democrats Assured, Election Night, 1992 April 15 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Editors, 1991 March 15 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Editors of Top 50 State Newspapers, 1993 September 10 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Fundraiser Meeting, 1992 August 31 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - Fundraising Lunch for Mike Moncrief Letter, 1993 August 30 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Health & Human Services Individuals, 1991 May 7 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - House Member (Democratic Nominee), 1992 March 12 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - House Primary Race Letters, 1992 March-April (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Income Tax Mailout, 1991 September 25 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Individuals Who Responded to Bullock’s Mailout (14th Street), 1991 May 6 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Individuals Who Wrote to Bullock Regarding Income Tax, 1991 April 29 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - Invitation to Serve on County Steering Committee, 1993 April 1 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Invitation to Serve on County Steering Committee, 1993 April 19 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Income Tax Mailings, 1991 May (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - List: Income Tax Through June 20, 1991, circa 1991 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Jack Robert’s Office, 1992 September 8 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Jan Bullock Trip, 1993 March 25 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - John Whitmire-Election Night, 1992 April 15 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - Johnson-Rayburn Committee Letter, 1992 September 17 (Box 41, Folder 30)
      - Key Individuals, 1991 March 29 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Letter of Congratulations-Harris County Democrats, 1991 October (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - “LOB” Lobbyists, pg. 1-82, 1993 June 7 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - “LOB” Lobbyists, pg. 83-164, 1993 June 7 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Lobby Invitation Letters (to “LOB” & “TSAE-Texas Society of Assoc. Executives) pg.1-50, 1993 June 7 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Lobby Invitation Letters (to “LOB” & Texas Society of Associational Executives (TSAE)) pg. 60-113, 1-7, 1993 June 7 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Luncheon in Houston, 1992 September (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Mailing List From Forrest Smith, Dallas, circa 1993 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Mailing List-Greater Houston Partnership, 1993 March 3 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Mailout Code Lists, circa 1991 May (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Mailout List Since July 1, 1990, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Media Letter, 1992 October (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Mike Moncrief Reception Letter, 1992 August 27 (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Other Elected Officials, 1993 June 24 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Pro-Choice (Cheryl) Letters, pgs. 1-40, 1992 January 31 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Pro-Choice (Cheryl) Letters, pgs. 41-80, 1992 January 31 (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Pro-Choice (Cheryl) Letters, pgs. 81-118, 1992 January 31 (Box 42, Folder 15)
      - Pro-Choice (Cheryl-1) Letters, 1992 January 31 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      - Reception Honoring Steve Carriker, 1993 September 13 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      - Republican Letters, 1992 March 11 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      - Returned Checks Due to Session Letters, 1993 June 7 (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - School Plan Survey, 1992 March 17 (Box 42, Folder 20)
      - Senate Democratic Campaign Committee Thank You Letters, 1992 May 4 (Box 42, Folder 21)
      - Senate Democratic Executive Committee, 1992 June 8 (Box 42, Folder 22)
      - Senator Letter, Franchise Tax, 1992 September 17 (Box 42, Folder 23)
      - Senator Montford Luncheon, 1993 November 29 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - Senators-NRA Endorsements, 1992 October (Box 42, Folder 25)
      - Special Senator Letters, 1992 March 11 (Box 42, Folder 26)
      - Statewide Media, 1991 March 25 (Box 42, Folder 27)
      - Statewide Media, 1991 April 2 (Box 42, Folder 28)
      - Statewide Media, 1991 April 8 (Box 42, Folder 29)
      - Steering 2, 1993 May 18 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Steering 2, 1993 May 20 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Steering Committee, 1993 April 5 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Steering Committee, 1993 April 20 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Steering Committee, 1993 April 21 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Steering Committee, 1993 April 26 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Steering Committee, 1993 April 28 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Steering Committee, 1993 May 4 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Steering Committee Thank You Letters, 1993 May 6 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Steering Committee Thank You Letters, 1993 May 13 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Steering Committee Thank You Letters, 1993 May 27 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Steering Committee Thank You Letters, 1993 June 15 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Steering Committee Thank You Letters, circa 1993 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Thank You for Help With Fundraising, 1993 September 28 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Texas Trial Lawyers Membership, 1992 January 29 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Texas’ Early Voting Program, 1992 February 21 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Those Agreeing to Serve on Steering Committee, 1993 July 7 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Those Who Came to Meeting and Made Pledge, 1993 June 22 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Those Who Came to Meeting and Did Not Make Pledge, 1993 June 22 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Those Unable to Attend Meeting, 1993 June 28 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Those Who Could Not Attend, pgs. 1-49, 1993 June 25 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Those Who Could Not Attend, pgs. 50-98, 1993 June 25 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - TV & Radio, 1991 March 13 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Women’s Rights, To Actors & Actresses, 1992 February 28 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Senators, 1992; 3
      - Whitmire, John, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - Zaffirini, Judith, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Endorsements, 1991-1994; 4
    The Endorsements subseries has two sub-subseries: Groups and Questionnaires. These sub-subseries contain candidate endorsements made by Bullock, correspondence and endorsements of Bob Bullock by groups and organizations, and questionnaires.
    - Groups, 1991-1994; 1
      - American Association of Retired Persons, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 27)
      - Endorsement List, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 28)
      - Texas AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 29)
      - Texas Health Care Association Political Action Committee, 1992 October (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Questionnaires, 1994; 2
      - A Master List, 1994 September (Box 43, Folder 31)
      - Apartment Association of Tarrant County, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 32)
      - Austin American-Statesman, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 33)
      - Citizens for Term Limits, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 34)
      - Coalition for North Texas Children, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 35)
      - Free Market Foundation, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      - Hill Country Cattlewomen, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Houston Chronicle, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Keep Austin Beautiful, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - League of Women Voters of Texas, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Mothers Against Drunk Driving, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - National Abortion and Reproduction Action League, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - National Council for Languages and International Studies, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Political Congress of African-American Women, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Taxpayers for Accountability, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Texas Association of Insurance Agents, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Texas Coalition of Black Democrats, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Texas Constitutional Coalition, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Texas Family Planning Association, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Texas Federation of Teachers, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Texas Legislative Service, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Texas Publishers Association, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Texas Women’s Political Caucus, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Voters For Choice, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Austin Lesbian/Gay Political Caucus, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Houston Gay/Lesbian Political Caucus, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - San Antonio Lesbian/Gay Political Caucus, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Tarrant County Lesbian/Gay Alliance, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Christian Mothers Society, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Citizens Against Lawsuit Abuse, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 24)
      - Clean Water Action, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - KJBC Midland-“Your Two Cents Worth”, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Providence Memorial Hospital-El Paso, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Texas Christian Coalition (Scott Fisher), 1994 (Box 44, Folder 28)
      - Americans For Truth in Education, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 29)
      - Austin Citizens Committee for Fair Immigration, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 30)
      - The Daily Tribune -Bay City, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 31)
      - Denton Record-Chronicle, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 32)
      - National Federation of Independent Business, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      - National Motorists-Texas Chapter, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 34)
      - P.E.A.C.E. Initiative-Domestic Violence, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 35)
      - Planned Parenthood of Houston/Southeast Texas, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 36)
      - Texas Abortion Rights Action League PAC, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 37)
      - Texas Agricultural Council, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 38)
      - Texas Association of College Teachers, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 39)
      - Texas Coalition for Initiative, Referendum and Recall, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 40)
      - Texas Motorcycle Rights Association, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 41)
      - United We Stand-Rockwall, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Financial, 1992-1994; 5
    - Bullock Contribution Letter, 1994 March 11 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Bullock Contribution Letter, 1994 May 16 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Democrat Letter, 1994 May 16 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Republican Letter, 1994 April 19 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Thank You Letters, 1992 September-December (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Invitations - Fundraisers, 1992-1994; 6
    - "A Bob Bullock Tradition", 1992 November 17 (Box 44, Folder 48)
    - Campaign Kick-off Event, 1993 October 14 (Box 44, Folder 49)
    - Dallas Fundraiser, Jess Hay, 1993 December 1 (Box 44, Folder 50)
    - Four Seasons Hotel, Austin (with Ann Richards), 1992 November 17 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - “Making His Mark on Texas”, 1994 September 13 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Reception at Four Seasons, 1991 October 23 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - San Antonio, 1994 May 18 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - The Stars of the Texas Senate, 1992 April 21 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Other- M.A.L.D.E.F. Dinner, 1992 Fall (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Issues, 1991-1993; 7
    The Issues subseries has three sub-subseries: Environment, Gay/Lesbian, and Others. Issues contains correspondence and subject files related to the political issues of the 1994 campaign. Bullock conducted extensive and thorough research into current events and topics that he felt might grow to importance during his campaigns.
    - Environment, 1991-1993; 1
      - Correspondence, 1991 February (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1992 April (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1993 May (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Gay/Lesbian, 1992-1993; 2
      - Correspondence, 1992 January (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1993 January (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1993 April (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Others, 1991-1993; 3
      - Abortion: Correspondence, 1992 June (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Alcohol & Drug Abuse, 1992 August (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Bingo, 1991 September-December (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Cigarettes, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Education: Correspondence, 1992 April (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Income Tax, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Income Tax, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Income Tax, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Income Tax: Correspondence, 1992 April (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Lottery, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - State Agencies: Correspondence, 1992 May (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Itineraries, 1991-1993; 8
    - Calendars, 1991 February (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Calendars, 1991 March (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Calendars, 1991 April (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Jan Bullock, 1993 February (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Jan Bullock, Main Street Tour, 1992 March (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Mosbacher, 1991-1994; 9
    - Contribution and Expense Report, 1991 January 1-June 30 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Contribution and Expense Report, 1991 July 15-December 31 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Contribution and Expense Report, 1992 January-June (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Campaign, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - General, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 33)